http://www.bernieprior.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
BERNIE PRIOR FOUNDATION PRIVACY POLICY SECTION 1 - EMAILWe value your privacy!We will never give, lease, sell or otherwise disclose your personal information. Period! Any information you give to Bernie Prior Foundation will be held with the utmost care. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions at all about our privacy policy, please email info@bernieprior.orgResale or Disclosure of Information to Third PartiesBernie Prior Foundation does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected by our website, including contact forms, download requests or email lists.Privacy of our Email ListsIndividuals join our mailing lists and are added to our email database using the forms provided on this web site or by signing up via paper forms at events with B Prior. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our lists to anyone. In addition, we configure our email software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized Bernie Prior Foundation Staff.Unsubscribe PolicyWe strive to only send e-mail to those who want to receive it. If you would not like to receive future e-mails from us, please use the 'unsubscribe' link located at the bottom of our email communications. SECTION 2 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about upcoming events, our store, and other updates.SECTION 3 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at info@bernieprior.org or mailing us at: Bernie Prior Foundation, 30 Governors Bay Teddington Rd, Governors Bay, Christchurch, 8971, New ZealandSECTION 4 - DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so.SECTION 6 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICESIn general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. Click for Foxy.io privacy policy. Click for Orderdesk privacy policy.In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms and Conditions.LinksWhen you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.SECTION 7 - SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@bernieprior.org or by mail at Bernie Prior Foundation, 30 Governors Bay Teddington Rd, Governors Bay, Christchurch, 8971, New Zealand
Top
Email Subscribe
Ways to support
Donations
Transcribing
Invite B
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Pricing is in New Zealand dollars unless otherwise specified.Copyright © 2017 B Prior Foundation
